<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:cc="http://cyber.law.harvard.edu/rss/creativeCommonsRssModule.html" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>Stories by Amirhossein Douzandeh on Medium</title>
        <description>Stories by Amirhossein Douzandeh on Medium</description>
        <link>https://medium.com/@amirzenoozi?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
        <image>
            <url>https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/fit/c/150/150/1*xH13aG8twCe3cSzdECKOqg.jpeg</url>
            <title>Stories by Amirhossein Douzandeh on Medium</title>
            <link>https://medium.com/@amirzenoozi?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
        </image>
        <generator>Medium</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:33:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://medium.com/@amirzenoozi/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml">
        </atom:link>
        <webMaster>yourfriends@medium.com</webMaster>
        <atom:link href="http://medium.superfeedr.com" rel="hub">
        </atom:link>
        <item>
            <title>Think and Document: Unlock the Secret to Passing Technical Interviews + Template</title>
            <description>&lt;div class="medium-feed-item"&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-image"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/think-and-document-unlock-the-secret-to-passing-technical-interviews-template-712a7d0fac4c?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2130/1*SQsFvziGYeFugkmtcc2knw.jpeg" width="2130"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-snippet"&gt;In the last few months, I was struggling with several interviews, and doing technical tasks. In this medium, I want to talk about how you&amp;#x2026;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/think-and-document-unlock-the-secret-to-passing-technical-interviews-template-712a7d0fac4c?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;Continue reading on Medium »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/think-and-document-unlock-the-secret-to-passing-technical-interviews-template-712a7d0fac4c?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/712a7d0fac4c</guid>
            <category>technical-interview</category>
            <category>interview-tips</category>
            <category>software-engineering</category>
            <category>hiring-process</category>
            <category>interview</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:36:21 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2024-08-01T16:36:21.808Z</atom:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Top 5 HR Interview Questions + Answers</title>
            <description>&lt;div class="medium-feed-item"&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-image"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/top-5-hr-interview-questions-answers-4bba93a21c8e?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/2600/1*JtmuKA63Rk4pLKTiIZ0yTg.jpeg" width="4500"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-snippet"&gt;If you are actively seeking a new job position, this Medium article is a must-read. Often, your first interview will be a brief meeting&amp;#x2026;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/top-5-hr-interview-questions-answers-4bba93a21c8e?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;Continue reading on Medium »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/top-5-hr-interview-questions-answers-4bba93a21c8e?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/4bba93a21c8e</guid>
            <category>interview-questions</category>
            <category>hr-interview</category>
            <category>interview</category>
            <category>tips-and-tricks</category>
            <category>interview-tips</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:17:46 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2024-06-14T14:17:46.410Z</atom:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Develop Your Personal MidJourney</title>
            <description>&lt;div class="medium-feed-item"&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-image"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/develop-your-personal-midjourney-38630f475480?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1400/1*XTuLiTWmyR1ZXXmHj-Oi1w.jpeg" width="1400"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-snippet"&gt;Hey there, fellow explorers of the digital realm! Have you noticed how AI tools are popping up all over the internet lately? It&amp;#x2019;s like&amp;#x2026;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/develop-your-personal-midjourney-38630f475480?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;Continue reading on Medium »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/develop-your-personal-midjourney-38630f475480?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/38630f475480</guid>
            <category>midjourney</category>
            <category>ai</category>
            <category>telegram-bot</category>
            <category>python-programming</category>
            <category>ai-text-to-image</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:52:36 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2024-03-14T17:52:36.204Z</atom:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Journey Through the Interview Realm: A Senior Developer’s Insight</title>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/journey-through-the-interview-realm-a-senior-developers-insight-4291282af0b7?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/4291282af0b7</guid>
            <category>front-end-development</category>
            <category>interview-questions</category>
            <category>programming</category>
            <category>interview-tips</category>
            <category>interview</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 14:36:28 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2024-02-11T14:36:28.825Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*bajxlE5TgMGkK2cXPY2T4Q.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;My Interview Experiences!!&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few weeks, I’ve been on a spree of Senior Front-End developer interviews. Here on Medium, I’m spilling the tea on my experiences to help you rock your interviews even better than I did! 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;🤔 How to Apply:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You think it might be the easiest step in your journey, but i have to disappoint you since I believe that it will be the most important one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/800/1*bgwjFc5iOR3hyRXD6hP16Q.gif" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href="https://dribbble.com/shots/3011000-Merlin-Wizard"&gt;Wizards by Rich Tabor | Dribbble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this crucial step, dive into the job description like you’re unraveling a mystery novel. Pinpoint the key skills they’re after — it’s like finding treasure on a map. Got something they’re looking for, like CI/CD wizardry? Flaunt it like a superhero! In my playbook, I spill the beans on these killer skills right in the second paragraph of my Cover Letter. After all, you’ve got about 20 seconds to amaze recruiters and keep them hooked on your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;🎙️ Interview&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crafting your Cover Letter and CV meet to their needs is like sending out a magnetic signal — they can’t help but get in touch and set up that exciting first interview. Now, when you’re in the hot seat with the Human Resource rock-stars, consider it a dance rather than a Q&amp;amp;A session. There’s no one-size-fits-all answer, but the secret sauce is understanding their culture and values. Give them what they crave, and you’re on your way to acing the interview!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congratulations, you’ve made it to the showtime where your code skills take center stage in front of your future senior teammates. The stage can be set in various ways — an online coding meeting, an offline coding adventure with a heads-up, or an offline coding session without any conditions. Now, brace yourself because the online coding is like a live performance with every keystroke scan. They’ll have you thinking out loud, giving them a VIP pass into your coding brain. It’s a bit harsh, I won’t lie, but hey, buckle up and be ready to shine under the spotlight!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;🙋🏻‍‍♀️ What Should YOU ask ?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the curtain falls on the interview, the spotlight turns to you — it’s your moment to flash with your questions and leave a lasting impression. This part is the grand finale, just as important as the rest because it tells how much this role means to you. It’s your chance to fire off questions like:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whats is your most important value in your culture?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;can I have a little more information about on-boarding process?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How you help your employee to boost themselves?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can I have some information about your feedback loop?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How can impress you during the first 3/6 months?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How can i help my other teammates?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How can i use the my teammates helps?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;All these questions are like the secret sauce — not overly technical and perfect to sprinkle at the end of your first interview. But, for the next rounds, it’s like tailoring a suit — fit it to your interviewer’s role. If they’re deep in the code, ask some tech questions. If they’re rocking a C-Level title, aim for the big picture — insights on where the company’s sailing in the next two years. It’s like crafting a custom playlist for every interview dance!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=4291282af0b7" width="1" height="1" alt=""&gt;</content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Decoding Persian News: Unleashing the Power of Analytics</title>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/decoding-persian-news-unleashing-the-power-of-analytics-86868be4756b?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/86868be4756b</guid>
            <category>perisan-news</category>
            <category>data-visualization</category>
            <category>visualization</category>
            <category>python-data-analysis</category>
            <category>python</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:54:38 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2023-07-25T11:54:38.830Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*GBCVi-VCviTgc_9oT5Wy8Q.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Looking At Persian NEWS With Analytics Glass&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to an exciting journey where we explore Persian News through the lens of analytics. Join me as we dive into the world of news analysis and uncover meaningful insights using charts and numbers. In this exploration, we aim to shed light on Persian News stories by harnessing the power of data visualization and quantitative analysis. By combining the art of storytelling with the precision of data, we’ll strive to unravel the narratives hidden within the news and present them in a captivating and informative manner. So, fasten your seat belts as we embark on this data-driven adventure, where we bridge the gap between news and analytics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;📃 Data Gathering From Web&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s begin by gathering data from the web. To accomplish this, we’ll utilize a script that we’ve developed. This script will assist us in collecting data from various news agencies. Throughout this process, we’ll be gathering a substantial number of news articles from several websites. To organize and store all this valuable data, we have opted to utilize SQLite, a reliable database management system. By leveraging the power of SQLite, we can effectively store and manage the collected data for further analysis. It’s worth mentioning that we have successfully stored a significant dataset of approximately &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;178&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;,480 articles. The fascinating part is that you can access this extensive dataset on the Kaggle website. Feel free to dive into the dataset and uncover intriguing insights and trends within the realm of news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/amirzenoozi/persian-news-dataset"&gt;Persian News Dataset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;📂 Exploring News By Service&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To begin, we process our data and determine the number of articles in each category, i.e. Service. After developing a Python script and processing the entire dataset, we observe that the International category consistently has a higher article count compared to other categories. Interestingly, the Arts and Media category ranks at the bottom of the list. To visualize this, we present a pie chart below showcasing the percentage distribution of all the categories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*7u75vojGVEO0OKPbK2KxxA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Categories Frequencies&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;🗓️ Exploring News By Published Date&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We believe it’s essential to explore this dataset by taking into account the publication dates of the articles. Our initial focus is on understanding the number of articles published each month, which allows us to uncover intriguing trends. Are the article numbers steadily increasing or decreasing over time? By delving into this analysis, we gain valuable insights into the dataset’s dynamics and discover interesting patterns that shape the article landscape. This temporal exploration adds an extra layer of understanding and reveals how article frequency evolves throughout the period of study. The picture below will illustrate this trend:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*sMG-7kDdcuXozKfGpy3-hA.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Date Time Frequencies&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;🏷️ Exploring News By Single tag&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This dataset has all the article tags in it. We thought it’d be really interesting to take a look at some of the most important tags among these articles. In this section, you’ll get to see the frequencies of these tags for each month, starting from the beginning date all the way to the end date. If you’re curious about how many articles contain a specific word, you can totally check out our Repository and customize the code to your liking. And hey, take a look at the plot below to see the number of articles that have the tag “The U.S.” It’s pretty neat, right? Happy writing!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*AEe8-Phxc6NMVhshtN10Ng.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Single Tag Frequencies&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;💻 End note&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is all about taking a fun beginner-level journey into the world of playing with data and discovering interesting information. If you’re someone who loves to dive into data and explore, this is the perfect read for you! And guess what? If you want to get your hands on this dataset and have some fun with it, just head over to the Kaggle Repository that I mentioned earlier. Oh, and here’s an exciting opportunity for you — you can actually contribute to the data gathering scripts in the repository below. Let’s embark on this data adventure together! 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/amirzenoozi/persian-news-crawler"&gt;GitHub - amirzenoozi/persian-news-crawler: Simple Script To Crawl Data From Persian News Agencies Including Fars, Mehr.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/amirzenoozi/persian-news-dataset"&gt;Persian News Dataset&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=86868be4756b" width="1" height="1" alt=""&gt;</content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Web Developers Roadmap in 2023: A Guide to the Latest Trends and Technologies</title>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/web-developers-roadmap-in-2023-a-guide-to-the-latest-trends-and-technologies-2c6ec74f1d9d?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/2c6ec74f1d9d</guid>
            <category>ai</category>
            <category>roadmaps</category>
            <category>web-development</category>
            <category>technology</category>
            <category>chatgpt</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:36:04 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2023-05-15T13:36:04.717Z</atom:updated>
            <content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1024/1*1JvjUVeJ-qFaJMeyYtkf_g.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Web Developers Roadmap Thumbnail&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a senior web developer, it’s important to keep up with the latest trends and technologies in the industry. The world of web development is constantly evolving, and it can be challenging to stay on top of everything. In this article, we’ll take a look at the web developer’s roadmap for 2023. We’ll explore the latest trends, technologies, and best practices that you should be aware of in order to stay ahead of the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;🎨 Web Development Frameworks&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Web development frameworks are an essential part of any web developer’s toolkit. They provide a set of tools and libraries that simplify the development process and enable developers to build more complex and dynamic web applications. In 2023, there will be several web development frameworks that will continue to gain popularity and dominate the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ReactJS is one of the most popular front-end frameworks used in web development today. It’s a JavaScript library that allows developers to build dynamic and interactive user interfaces. ReactJS is widely used in the industry and has a large and active community of developers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angular is another popular front-end framework that has gained a lot of traction in recent years. It’s a comprehensive framework that provides a full suite of tools for building complex web applications. Angular is known for its flexibility and scalability, making it an ideal choice for large-scale projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vue.js is a lightweight and easy-to-learn front-end framework that has been gaining popularity in recent years. It’s a flexible and powerful framework that allows developers to build complex web applications with ease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;👩🏻‍💻 Backend Development&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Backend development is an essential part of web development that deals with the server-side of web applications. In 2023, there will be several technologies and trends in backend development that will gain traction in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Node.js is a popular server-side technology that is widely used in web development today. It’s a JavaScript runtime that allows developers to build scalable and high-performance web applications. Node.js has a large and active community of developers and is known for its speed and scalability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Serverless architecture is a new trend in backend development that is gaining popularity in the industry. Serverless architecture allows developers to build and run applications without the need for traditional servers. This technology provides greater flexibility and scalability, and reduces infrastructure costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;👨🏻‍💻Database Technologies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Database technologies are an essential part of web development that deals with the storage and retrieval of data. In 2023, there will be several database technologies that will gain traction in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MongoDB is a popular NoSQL database that is widely used in web development today. It’s a document-oriented database that provides high performance and scalability. MongoDB is known for its flexibility and ease-of-use, making it an ideal choice for web applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GraphQL is a new technology that is gaining traction in the industry. It’s a query language for APIs that provides a more efficient, powerful, and flexible approach to data fetching. GraphQL is known for its ability to reduce network overhead and simplify client-side development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;☁️ Cloud Technologies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cloud technologies have been transforming the way web applications are developed and deployed. In 2023, there will be several cloud technologies that will continue to dominate the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a cloud platform that provides a wide range of services for web development. It’s a popular choice for web developers because of its scalability, reliability, and flexibility. AWS provides a wide range of services, including compute, storage, database, and networking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Azure is another popular cloud platform that provides a wide range of services for web development. It’s known for its scalability, security, and hybrid capabilities. Azure provides a wide range of services, including compute, storage, database, and networking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud Platform (GCP) is a cloud platform that provides a wide range&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;😎 Finally&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the field of web development is constantly evolving, and staying up to date with the latest trends and technologies is essential for success. The roadmap for web developers in 2023 will require proficiency in fundamental web development skills such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, as well as knowledge of popular front-end frameworks such as React, Angular, and Vue. Back-end development skills such as server-side programming, database management, and API development will also be in high demand. In addition, a focus on security, accessibility, and user experience will continue to be critical components of successful web development. By prioritizing continued learning and keeping up with the latest trends, web developers can position themselves for success in 2023 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My GitHub Profile:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/amirzenoozi"&gt;amirzenoozi - Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="https://medium.com/_/stat?event=post.clientViewed&amp;referrerSource=full_rss&amp;postId=2c6ec74f1d9d" width="1" height="1" alt=""&gt;</content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Find Dominant Common Color With Telegram Bot</title>
            <description>&lt;div class="medium-feed-item"&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-image"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/find-dominant-common-color-with-telegram-bot-b5bfad2b8fe8?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1400/1*WH1Kyb4Ixpf8JnJpWf8bzg.jpeg" width="1400"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-snippet"&gt;In the last few days, I decided to play with the telegram bot but I need to have a simple scenario for my application so I think &amp;#x201C;finding&amp;#x2026;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/find-dominant-common-color-with-telegram-bot-b5bfad2b8fe8?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;Continue reading on Medium »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/find-dominant-common-color-with-telegram-bot-b5bfad2b8fe8?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/b5bfad2b8fe8</guid>
            <category>opencv-python</category>
            <category>development</category>
            <category>telegram</category>
            <category>programming</category>
            <category>python</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 08:39:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2023-11-30T20:03:02.024Z</atom:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ZSH Config On Windows Terminal Application</title>
            <description>&lt;div class="medium-feed-item"&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-image"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/zsh-config-on-windows-terminal-application-40a2bd213d6d?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1400/1*D7DcKBHF8waYUAP3ogzUZQ.png" width="1400"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-snippet"&gt;Have you ever try to connect to server that use ZSH as a terminal&amp;#xA0;? in this case if you use Linux base OS you just need to install the&amp;#x2026;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/zsh-config-on-windows-terminal-application-40a2bd213d6d?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;Continue reading on Medium »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/zsh-config-on-windows-terminal-application-40a2bd213d6d?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/40a2bd213d6d</guid>
            <category>powershell</category>
            <category>terminal-windows</category>
            <category>windows</category>
            <category>oh-my-zsh</category>
            <category>bash</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 10:36:46 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2022-12-03T08:54:47.862Z</atom:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How To Have Angular Environment Structure in React Applications Without CRA</title>
            <description>&lt;div class="medium-feed-item"&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-image"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/how-to-have-angular-environment-structure-in-react-applications-without-cra-e970443e9068?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1400/1*ctW9S9Y5nAAqL7a45Dk4AA.png" width="1400"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-snippet"&gt;Use Angular Environment Variable Structure Inside your React Applications With Single Easy Step, Lets Start To Code&amp;#x2026;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/how-to-have-angular-environment-structure-in-react-applications-without-cra-e970443e9068?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;Continue reading on Medium »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/how-to-have-angular-environment-structure-in-react-applications-without-cra-e970443e9068?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/e970443e9068</guid>
            <category>reactjs</category>
            <category>environment</category>
            <category>webpack</category>
            <category>react</category>
            <category>angular</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 18:47:35 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2022-12-03T09:03:27.977Z</atom:updated>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Make a simple URL shortener app with Node.js &amp; Express.js + Rest API</title>
            <description>&lt;div class="medium-feed-item"&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-image"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/make-a-simple-url-shortener-app-with-node-js-express-js-rest-api-5cce40413d2b?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1400/1*L3tLt-PRP6hs--1oiq6Fbg.png" width="1400"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-snippet"&gt;Have you ever though to learn a Node.js&amp;#xA0;? Trying out simple projects such as ToDoApps &amp;amp; WeathersApp will help you learn new things quickly&amp;#x2026;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="medium-feed-link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/make-a-simple-url-shortener-app-with-node-js-express-js-rest-api-5cce40413d2b?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2"&gt;Continue reading on Medium »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
            <link>https://amirzenoozi.medium.com/make-a-simple-url-shortener-app-with-node-js-express-js-rest-api-5cce40413d2b?source=rss-1db5d7e2f442------2</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://medium.com/p/5cce40413d2b</guid>
            <category>url-shorteners</category>
            <category>expressjs</category>
            <category>nodejs</category>
            <category>javascript</category>
            <category>mongodb</category>
            <dc:creator>Amirhossein Douzandeh</dc:creator>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 15:49:56 GMT</pubDate>
            <atom:updated>2023-11-30T20:00:49.021Z</atom:updated>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>